(Leonard:)so this issue is resolved.
(Leonard:)And I'd just like to point out that
(Leonard:)even though the sweater
was uncomfortable,
(Leonard:)I didn't use it as an excuse
to antagonize everyone around me.
(Howard:)You know, you could reimburse
the video store owner's next of kin.
Or it's resolved!
(Sheldon:)Hey, that next of kin thing
sounds pretty good.
(Howard:)I believe this is yours.
(Raj:)Can I ask you guys a question?
(Raj:)So, I'm seeing Lucy tomorrow night,
and I've never hung out
(Raj:)with someone who broke up with me.
How do you do it?
(Howard:)You can't let her know you're
hurting. The key is confidence.
(Raj:)Why is the key always confidence?
(Raj:)How come it's never
love handles and flop sweat?
(Bernadette:)If this girl hurt you so much, are
you sure you want to see her again?
(Howard:)Well, if I may,
he has so little self-respect
(Howard:)and is so desperate
for the smallest crumb of affection,